<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cristóbal Carnero Liñán</title>
    <link>http://xn--cristbal-z3a.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cristóbal Carnero Liñán</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://xn--cristbal-z3a.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>http://xn--cristbal-z3a.com/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xn--cristbal-z3a.com/cv/</guid>
      <description>Download .PDF ⬇
 “Creativity is intelligence having fun.” – Albert Einstein
  Phone: +34 655 52 79 11 Email: ccarnerolinan@gmail.com Personal web: http://cristóbal.com LinkedIn: http://es.linkedin.com/in/ccarnerolinan/ Date of birth: 12th February, 1981  Summary More than 10 years of professional experience in the software industry and university research groups. Expertise in develop, deploy and manage server-side software and web services.
Education  2009 – 2011 Master in Software Engineer and Artificial Intelligence, Universidad de Málaga.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Mukabe</title>
      <link>http://xn--cristbal-z3a.com/post/mukabe_en/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xn--cristbal-z3a.com/post/mukabe_en/</guid>
      <description>Lee la versión en castellano
Introducing Those who knows me realize that I am always working in a lot of side projects, about computing or other crazy things. And Mukabe matches both groups. But this is one of those crazy things that makes more sense the more you think about it.
The idea born in a dream. Next morning I begin to make sense of it, and some days later I started coding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentación de Mukabe</title>
      <link>http://xn--cristbal-z3a.com/post/mukabe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xn--cristbal-z3a.com/post/mukabe/</guid>
      <description>Read the English version
Introducción Los que me conocen saben que siempre ando con un montón de proyectos paralelos, ya sean de informática o cualquier otra locura que se me ocurra. Y Mukabe es una de esas locuras. Pero es de esas locuras que tienen más sentido cuanto más lo piensas.
La idea surgió en un sueño. A la mañana siguiente empecé a darle sentido a lo que había soñado, y unos días después empecé a programar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentación de RegaloInteligente.com</title>
      <link>http://xn--cristbal-z3a.com/post/regalointeligente/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xn--cristbal-z3a.com/post/regalointeligente/</guid>
      <description>Introducción Después de mucho tiempo de trabajo, es un placer presentar mi último proyecto: RegaloInteligente.com. Esta idea nació hace ya casi diez años, aunque por aquel entonces era algo totalmente distinto. En aquel momento se quedó en el tintero porque no había una forma clara de monetizar la idea. En 2013 retomé el concepto pero lo transformé en lo que terminó siendo: un buscador de regalos. Pero no di con la tecla de cómo hacer la clasificación inteligente de los regalos, y entre la avalancha de otros proyectos quedó aparcado.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generate Curriculum Vitae in multiple formats</title>
      <link>http://xn--cristbal-z3a.com/post/resume-generator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xn--cristbal-z3a.com/post/resume-generator/</guid>
      <description>Motivation In the last week I&amp;rsquo;ve been updating my CV and finally I managed to build a nice one using the moderncv class for LaTeX. You can see it here. The problem was when someone asked me the Word version of it (don&amp;rsquo;t ask me why). As I wanted to have the curriculum vitae in this site updated too I look for a way to have my resume in multiple formats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>http://xn--cristbal-z3a.com/post/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xn--cristbal-z3a.com/post/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Welcome Hi, my name is Cristóbal and this is the first post of what I hope will be a very useful blog, filled with tips, snippets, tutorials, and much more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>http://xn--cristbal-z3a.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xn--cristbal-z3a.com/about/</guid>
      <description>When I was 13 years old I found in my house a little manual about programming in GW-BASIC. Making something with it was a nightmare but also a lot of fun. Just after I used Turbo Basic, QBasic, QuickBASIC, Visual Basic,&amp;hellip; I usually did some programs with beautiful GUIs and databases. But then I discover Turbo Pascal. Things got serious with it, and I started doing graphical things.
Firstly I began doing very simple videogames, but then I discover the demoscene.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal projects</title>
      <link>http://xn--cristbal-z3a.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xn--cristbal-z3a.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>Mukabe Mukabe is the new way of navigate through information, the new social and online organization, and the new way to get visibility for you, your projects or your company.
https://mukabe.com
Read more in this blog post: Introduction to Mukabe.
RegaloInteligente 
Gift search engine.
 Web application Android app  Free software projects WooDPD WordPress Plugin to integrate DPD purchases in WooCommerce.
http://woodpdplugin.com
OrigamiPress Blog tool, publishing platform, and CMS developed in Python.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>