<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title>Posts on Crist칩bal Carnero Li침치n </title>
      <generator uri="https://hugo.spf13.com">Hugo</generator>
    <link>http://xn--cristbal-z3a.com/post/index.xml/</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
    
    <updated>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 00:00:00 UTC</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generate Curriculum Vitae in multiple formats</title>
      <link>http://xn--cristbal-z3a.com/post/resume-generator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xn--cristbal-z3a.com/post/resume-generator/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/post-cv-generator.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Motivation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the last week I&amp;rsquo;ve been updating my CV and finally I managed to build a nice one using the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ctan.org/pkg/moderncv&#34;&gt;moderncv&lt;/a&gt; class for LaTeX. You can see it &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cristobalcl/resume/raw/master/output/cristobal-resume.pdf&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. The problem was when someone asked me the &lt;strong&gt;Word&lt;/strong&gt; version of it (don&amp;rsquo;t ask me why). As I wanted to have the &lt;a href=&#34;/cv&#34;&gt;curriculum vitae&lt;/a&gt; in this site updated too I look for a way to have my resume in multiple formats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_1&#34;&gt;My take&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What was the solution? Well, maybe it&amp;rsquo;s overkill but, anyway&amp;hellip; This is the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cristobalcl/resume&#34;&gt;source repository&lt;/a&gt; of the scripts that generate my curriculum in several formats. Firstly there is a file called &lt;code&gt;resume.yaml&lt;/code&gt; that have all the information about my CV in &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.yaml.org/&#34;&gt;YAML&lt;/a&gt;. Then there is a directory called &lt;code&gt;templates&lt;/code&gt;. The templates are &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.makotemplates.org/&#34;&gt;Mako&lt;/a&gt; files.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two scripts are used to generate the files. One of them is a Python program that read the information from the YAML file and feeds the different templates to render versions of the CV in Markdown and LaTeX formats. The other one is a simple Bash script that deals with temporary directories, runs &lt;a href=&#34;http://johnmacfarlane.net/pandoc/&#34;&gt;Pandoc&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;code&gt;pdflatex&lt;/code&gt;. Also, it compress the final PDF file.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this moment it generates the resume in PDF, docx, ODT and Markdown format for &lt;a href=&#34;http://gohugo.io/&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt;. In the &lt;code&gt;deploy.sh&lt;/code&gt; script of the repository of this web I&amp;rsquo;ve added a &lt;code&gt;wget&lt;/code&gt; command to get the last version of the CV every time the web is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This system works, but it has some problems. For example, there is no easy way to add formatting in the resume, so I added a little hack: you can use &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;*&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;*&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; tags to emphasize. Another problem is that in Pandoc&amp;rsquo;s Markdown you can not specify image size or alignment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_2&#34;&gt;Conclusions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So that&amp;rsquo;s it. You can &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/cristobalcl/resume/fork&#34;&gt;fork&lt;/a&gt; it and write your own curriculum in the &lt;code&gt;resume.yaml&lt;/code&gt;. Also you can add more templates. A HTML template would be very easy to do, for example, but also you can use Pandoc to generate it from the Markdown version. Something I&amp;rsquo;ve been considering is a way to export or import the LinkeId information using its API&amp;hellip; Another possibility is to translate automatically to several languages. I leave this to you ;)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>http://xn--cristbal-z3a.com/post/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2015 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://xn--cristbal-z3a.com/post/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;toc_0&#34;&gt;Welcome&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hi, my name is &lt;strong&gt;Crist칩bal&lt;/strong&gt; and this is the first post of what I hope will be a very useful blog, filled with tips, snippets, tutorials, and much more.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>